<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

 
  
  <!-- Misc -->

  <AA_AsexualHatched>{0} has reproduced asexually.</AA_AsexualHatched>
    <AA_AsexualHatchedEgg>{0} has sporulated.</AA_AsexualHatchedEgg>

  
    <!-- Incidents -->
  <LetterLabelColossalAerofleetPasses>Colossal Aerofleet</LetterLabelColossalAerofleetPasses>
  <LetterColossalAerofleetPasses>A strange floating creature bounces around in the distance, blundering around the landscape.\n\nA small horde of smaller specimens seem to be attracted to it, and follow it at a short distance.\n\nThey seem to be mostly harmless, and will probably leave the area when they have fed.</LetterColossalAerofleetPasses>
  
  <LetterLabelSkyAsteroid>Strange asteroid</LetterLabelSkyAsteroid>
  <LetterSkyAsteroid>A small, strange asteroid seems to have entered the atmosphere of this planet. Impact is inminent.</LetterSkyAsteroid>
  
  <LetterLabelBumbledroneMigration>Bumbledrone migration</LetterLabelBumbledroneMigration>
  <LetterBumbledroneMigration>A small group of bumbledrones, led by a bumbledrone queen, has entered this area.\n\nBumbledrones are generally not aggressive, unless threatened.\n\nThey will probably leave this area after a while in search of a quieter place, since the colony is too noisy for them.</LetterBumbledroneMigration>

  
  <LetterLabelManhuntingArcticLion>Stalking Arctic Lion</LetterLabelManhuntingArcticLion>
  <ManhuntingArcticLion>An arctic lion is stalking one of your colonists from the shadows.\n\nIt will be almost invisible until it decides to attack and is damaged by your colonists. Colonists that are drafted and alert and automatic defenses will be able to detect it, so you should prepare quickly! \n\nArctic lions are fearsome, genetically engineered creatures bred for combat in cold climates.</ManhuntingArcticLion>
  
  <LetterLabelBlizzariskClutchMother>Blizzarisk clutch mother</LetterLabelBlizzariskClutchMother>
  <BlizzariskClutchMother>A huge spider like creature called a Blizzarisk, adapted to cold climates, wanders through this territory.\n\nThis Blizzarisk seems to be of much bigger size than usual, and is carrying a clutch of eggs on its back. This sounds like a recipe for disaster if not dealt with quickly.</BlizzariskClutchMother>
  
  <LetterLabelDunealiskClutchMother>Dunealisk clutch mother</LetterLabelDunealiskClutchMother>
  <DunealiskClutchMother>A huge spider like creature called a Dunealisk, adapted to hot climates, wanders through this territory.\n\nThis Dunealisk seems to be of much bigger size than usual, and is carrying a clutch of eggs on its back. This sounds like a recipe for disaster if not dealt with quickly.</DunealiskClutchMother>
 
  <LetterLabelFeraliskClutchMother>Feralisk clutch mother</LetterLabelFeraliskClutchMother>
  <FeraliskClutchMother>A huge spider like creature called a Feralisk wanders through this territory.\n\nThis Feralisk seems to be of much bigger size than usual, and is carrying a clutch of eggs on its back. This sounds like a recipe for disaster if not dealt with quickly.</FeraliskClutchMother>
 
   <LetterLabelSummitCrab>Summit Crab</LetterLabelSummitCrab>
  <SummitCrab>The ground trembles as a massive hermit crab living inside a huge boulder drags itself across this region.\n\nThe gargantuan bouldermit isn't hostile, but it is almost impervious to gunfire and it will lay waste to anything in its path if not stopped.</SummitCrab>
  
  <LetterLabelCactipinePod>Strange drop pod</LetterLabelCactipinePod>
  <CactipineDropPod>The air roars with the unmistakable sound of a drop pod during re-entry. Scanners detect life signs inside, but they are REALLY weird life signs, as if the scanner couldn't tell whether it is animal or plant life.</CactipineDropPod>
  
  <LetterLabelGallatrossPasses>Gallatross wanders</LetterLabelGallatrossPasses>
  <LetterGallatrossPasses>Legends tell of a creature so huge and powerful that entire tribes fled at the sight of it. Such legends were inspired by the Gallatross, an inmense creature with a ravenous appetite. Perhaps it is somehow related to the elusive Thrumbo? Such questions are probably impossible to answer.</LetterGallatrossPasses>
  
  <LetterLabelBlackHiveAttack>Black hive attack</LetterLabelBlackHiveAttack>
  <LetterBlackHiveAttack>Insectoids in the rim are genetically altered organisms designed to fight mechanoid invasions. The Black Hive was the best of the best, designed to be much more aggressive than usual, and capable of laying siege to impregnable mechanoid fortresses. Existing insectoid species were improved and several new species were created and added to the Hive to increase its lethality.\n\nA group of Black Hive insectoids has tunneled to this location, and will attack your base immediately.</LetterBlackHiveAttack>
  
  
  <!-- Animal Products -->
  
  <HyperweaveDesc>Hyperweave production</HyperweaveDesc>
  <AA_UraniumCrystalsDesc>Uranium crystal loosening</AA_UraniumCrystalsDesc>
  <StoneChunkDesc>Random stone chunk loosening</StoneChunkDesc>
  <StoneBlockDesc>Random stone block loosening</StoneBlockDesc>
  <MedicinalQuillDesc>Medicinal quill growth</MedicinalQuillDesc>
  <DevilstrandDesc>Devilstrand production</DevilstrandDesc>
  <SynthreadDesc>Synthread production</SynthreadDesc>
  <BoomthreadDesc>Boomthread production</BoomthreadDesc>
  <ChunkSlagSteelDesc>Steel chunk loosening</ChunkSlagSteelDesc>
  <RawMushrooms>Raw mushrooms growth</RawMushrooms>
  <AA_MealNutrientPaste>Nutrient paste production</AA_MealNutrientPaste>
  <AA_Wood>Time to "trim" trees</AA_Wood>


  
  <!-- Mod Settings -->
  
  <allowBlackHive>Allow Black Hive raids</allowBlackHive>
  <allowStalkingLions>Allow Stalking Arctic Lion attacks</allowStalkingLions>
  <allowCactipineDroppods>Allow Cactipine droppod event</allowCactipineDroppods>
  <allowSpiderClutchMothers>Allow spider clutch mothers event</allowSpiderClutchMothers>
  <allowAerofleet>Allow aerofleet migrations</allowAerofleet>
  <allowGallatross>Allow gallatross migrations</allowGallatross>
  <allowSummitCrab>Allow summit crab event</allowSummitCrab>
  <allowBumbledrones>Allow bumbledrone migrations</allowBumbledrones>
  <allowFrostmiteCorpses>Allow frostmites digging corpses on their own</allowFrostmiteCorpses>
  <allowAsteroids>Allow Arcturan Sky eel asteroids impacting</allowAsteroids>













</LanguageData>