<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Alpha Animals</name>
	<supportedVersions>
      <li>1.0</li>
      <li>1.1</li>
	   <li>1.2</li>
   </supportedVersions>
   <modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	
	<loadAfter>
	  
      <li>smashphil.boats</li>
    </loadAfter>
	<author>Sarg, AFriend, milon, Skullywag and kaptain_kavern</author>
	
		<packageId>sarg.alphaanimals</packageId>

	<description>Adds multiple unique new animals to Rimworld.
	
&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;

Adds 93 new, vanilla-friendly creatures to the diverse biomes of your Rimworlds. The philosophy of this mod is that every new creatures tries to bring some new mechanic into the game, whether it be walking tanks, living resource farm, indestructible plant monsters, night time stalkers, or plain speedy giant spiders. Some of the mechanics are simple, others much more complex.

These animals will spawn in certain biomes, some others will only be available via traders. You'll have to explore to find them all! The Alpha Biomes is a companion mod that adds several new alien biomes to house these weird creatures.

Bear in mind that spawn probabilities have been calculated with no other animal mods installed. If you have, for example, Animal Collab Project, less animals from this mod will appear, obviously.

The mod will also add new insects in a new faction, the Black Hive. Raids from that faction can be disabled via Mod Options.

&lt;size=24&gt;Issues&lt;/size&gt;

There shouldn't be any. Balance is obviously always a concern, although it has been playtested. Feel free to tell me if you think something is too wacky.

&lt;size=24&gt;Plans for the future&lt;/size&gt;
Obviously, more animals!

&lt;size=24&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;
Compatible with A Dog Said... 
Compatible with the implants from Genetic Rim
Compatible with cloth production in Vegetable Garden Project (VGP)
Compatible with Alpha Biomes (duh)
Compatible with Nature's Pretty Sweet
Compatible with Advanced Biomes
Compatible with Rainbeau Realistic Planets
Compatible with Lords of the Rims - Elves (mallorn biome)
Compatible with Boats
Uses Harmony (dependency)


&lt;size=24&gt;Credit&lt;/size&gt;
Original creature graphics: A_Friend, aka SentientLine
Original implementation and programming: milon, Skullywag and kaptain_kavern 
Some sounds by Mike Koenig at http://soundbible.com
Some sounds by PsychoBird at http://soundbible.com
Some sounds by Stephan Schutze at http://soundbible.com
Some animal sounds by LiamG_SFX, wisslgisse, M4D3R0 and roubignolle at https://freesound.org
Fireball Graphic created by StarsteelGaming at OpenGameArt.org (2018)
Using NocturnalAnimals DLL by XeoNovaDan

&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;

v2.5: Added 2 new animals, 2 new mechanoids and 5 retextures (26/08/20)
v2.4: Added 4 new animals. Varios bugfixes (31/05/20)
v2.3: Added 4 new animals. Redesigned Bumbledrones. Added many new exotic implants such as tentacles and wings to A Dog Said (25/04/20)
v2.2: Added 5 new animals (mechanoids). Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (29/03/20)
v2.1: Added 8 new animals. Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (18/03/20)
v2.0: Updated for RimWorld 1.1 (21/02/20)
v1.9: Added three new "bioship" animals. These can be created if you have the Boats mod installed, and act as a means of transportation. (21/12/19)
v1.808: Added A Dog Said for latest animals (10/12/19)
v1.807: Added options toggle for latest animals, and an option to remove all animal particles (gasses) to reduce lag (08/11/19)
v1.806: Minor bugfixing (22/10/19)
v1.8: Added 6 new animals. Added Meadow Ave sounds. Added floating behaviour. Added crepuscular behaviour (18/10/19)
v1.701: Typo fixing. (17/09/19)
v1.7: Added 4 new animals for the new Alpha Biomes biome. (16/09/19)
v1.6: Added 2 new animals for the new Alpha Biomes biome. Changed nocturnal animal code (thanks XND!). Some bugfixing. (09/09/19)
v1.5: Added 7 new animals to populate the newly released Alpha Biomes mod. (21/08/19)
v1.402: Hopefully last change to mod options. Changed Sky Eel min temp (14/06/19)
v1.401: Fixed mod options. Updated Modcheck to make it compatible with new RW version (31/05/19)
v1.4: Added mod settings to select which animals should or shouldn't appear on the map as wild spawns (18/05/19)
v1.301: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (16/05/19)
v1.3: Added five new animals. Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (16/04/19)
v1.2: Added four new animals. Added compatibility with Advanced Biomes Mod (06/04/19)
v1.1: Added visual Giddy-Up! saddles to mosty rideable creatures. The Meadow Ave is not being rendered correctly so it will need a later update (02/04/19)
v1.096: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (06/03/19)
v1.094: Small bugfix to re-balance Meadow Aves (05/02/19)
v1.093: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (31/01/19)
v1.09: Four new animals added! Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (01/12/18)
v1.08: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (12/11/18)
v1.07: Two new animals added! Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (04/11/18)
v1.06: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (31/10/18)
v1.05: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (29/10/18)
v1.04: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (24/10/18)
v1.03: Five new animals added! Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (23/10/18)
v1.02: Bugfixing and balance tweaks. Full changelog on GitHub (22/10/18)
v1.0: Rimworld 1.0 version (17/10/18)
v0.1: Prerelease

	

	</description>
</ModMetaData>